all the three IP, Y and B files,
and you're free to collaborate with your classmates,
but just write the name of the people you collaborated
with at the top of the worksheet.
So I'll just introduce the worksheets to you guys.
So worksheet two is on simple linear regression
and multiple linear regression.
You'll have to just plot a scatter plot
and build a linear regression model.
You have to check if it follows the OLS assumptions
and validate the linear regression model.
Then the multiple linear regression,
you have to plot a correlogram
and check which contributes most to the target variable
and build a multiple linear regression model
based on that.
The worksheet two B is based on ridge regression,
lasso and elastic regression.
You'll have to build all these three models.
So worksheet two C is on logistic regression.
You'll have to just build a logistic regression model
and plot the ROC curve and AOC value.
So the last day to submit will be 20th September.
Before constructing the correlogram,
you can use anything label encoding or one-hundred encoding.
Just convert it.
You can ask your doubts in the chat
or you can raise your hand, we'll unmute you.
There will be another TA session
four or five days before the deadline.
So by then your portion should be covered.
So you'll be able to solve and ask more questions that time.
But if you have any doubts,
you can put it in the chat or unmute,
raise your hand, we'll unmute.
You can just use the libraries to build the model.
Like for linear regression model, you can use LM
and for worksheet two B, you can use GLM net.
You need not build one from scratch,
just import the library.
You can use any library you want.
There is no completion on the syntax.
You can use any syntax or any libraries you want.
Which question three, the OLS assumptions?
Yeah, for OLS assumptions, you can do like three.
You can check if the residuals are,
residuals follow the normal distribution.
You can check for homosodacity
and you can check for the linear relationship.
You can do three, that's enough.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah, if you put it as a markdown,
it will be better and professional.
If you answer in terms of, if it's a code,
then use the code of both graphs and write ups
because try to add your analysis as much as possible,
not only code.
So add comments or a markdown
for whatever you are plotting.
Agnes, you can unmute and ask the question.
Yes.
You want to check that open right?
You need to,
you can take a spot.
Yeah, that's what I answered.
You can add a markdown cell and answer in that cell
after each question.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah, Rohan, the histogram of residuals
is enough for normal distribution.
Do add like a text cell,
seeing some just don't add the code guys.
Just don't write the code for plotting histogram
and leave it like this.
Do add analysis of the graph.
Yeah, markdown code, markdown code.
Just add a markdown cell
whenever you want to write the text or analysis
and code cells when you want to execute the code.
Are there any more questions or we shall end them?
There'll be another TA session
four or five days before the deadline.
So you guys should,
the portion should be covered by then.
So you guys should be able to solve that.
We'll let you know soon.
Do you guys have any more questions?
Okay, then we'll end the meeting.
Thank you for joining us.
If any of you have missed the first part of this session,
we'll make the recording available.
You guys can catch up with that.
Thank you.